bsr.org 2018-01-26

# BSR

## Privacy Policy

BSR is committed to your right to privacy and to the ethical use of information online. We adhere strictly to the following privacy practices.

Last updated on : Added information about Google Adwords Remarketing Service.

* * *

### No release of personally identifiable information to third parties

We do not rent, sell, give, exchange, or otherwise share personally identifiable information with other individuals or organizations.

### Personally identifiable information is collected only on a voluntary basis

Personally identifiable information such your name, postal address, telephone number, or credit card number are collected only if you "opt in" by choosing to give us this information on a voluntary basis such as signing up to our newsletters, blog, and job feeds.

### We do collect "aggregate data," that is, group data with no personal identifiers

We use this aggregate data to help us understand how the site is being used and to improve its usability. We also use it to enhance the quality and availability of products and services we offer. We also, with explicit permission, use aggregate data from online surveys you choose to fill out for research and publication purposes.

### How we use the information

Personally identifiable information you choose to give us will only be used to:

  * Process membership applications
  * Process billing and orders for products/services you choose to purchase on our site
  * Send you product information and occasional special offers or announcements from select BSR partners.
  * Add you to our mailing lists.

We will only use the information you give us on the website for the purposes described in this privacy policy.

### Cookies

We do not use cookies to collect information about you. We do use temporary or session cookies to help you navigate our site, keep you logged into our website, and to analyze website traffic patterns. Sometimes third-party services, outside of our control, will use Cookies for tracking purposes.

### Google AdWords Remarketing Service

From time to time, our websites may use a remarketing advertising service. Our remarketing service is provided by Google to show our ads on websites across the internet. With remarketing, you may see ads for our products, services, or events you have previously looked at.

Here’s an example of how remarketing works: Suppose you visit a website that sells watches, but you do not buy a watch on your first visit to that website. The website owner might like to encourage you to revisit their site and buy a watch by showing you their ads again on other websites you visit.

We use remarketing for similar purposes so you may see advertisements for our products, services, or events like the annual BSR Conference as you search the Internet. For this to happen, Google will read a cookie that is already in your browser, or they will place a cookie in your browser when you visit one of our websites or other sites using remarketing.

This can only happen if your browser is set to let it happen. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb), and if you would like, you can opt out of interest-based advertising permanently by changing your privacy options in your web browser.

### Links

The BSR site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each site they visit. BSR's privacy statement applies only to information collected by our website.

### BSR Conference

The BSR Conference may be audio or video recorded, posted as a podcast, photographed, published, and archived. As such, Conference attendees grant BSR permission for use of images.

## Data Protection

To learn more, please [download our data protection policy](https://bsr.app.box.com/BSRdpp).
